{
    "subject": "resource/WSLR-LP",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.wslr.org",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of WSLR-LP is http://www.wslr.org.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9695900678634644,
            "question": "Which URL leads to the homepage of WSLR-LP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.956760585308075,
            "question": "Where can you find the homepage of WSLR-LP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547886848449707,
            "question": "What is the URL of WSLR-LP's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9363960027694702,
            "question": "Provide the web address for WSLR-LP."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9270032048225403,
            "question": "If you want to visit the homepage of WSLR-LP, what URL should you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9246290326118469,
            "question": "What is the official website for WSLR-LP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9110150337219238,
            "question": "What website address belongs to WSLR-LP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8852311372756958,
            "question": "If you search online for WSLR-LP, what website address would likely appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8782919049263,
            "question": "Where online can you access information about WSLR-LP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8498916029930115,
            "question": "How can you find the official information about WSLR-LP?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of WSLR-LP is http://www.wslr.org.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7470_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where online can you access information about WSLR-LP?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7470_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you search online for WSLR-LP, what website address would likely appear?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7470_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What website address belongs to WSLR-LP?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7470_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7470_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the statement \"The homepage of WSLR-LP is https://www.wslr.org.\" is supported by the documents.\n\nAfter analyzing the documents, I found that this statement is indeed supported by the following text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7470/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt:\n\n\"Visit https://www.WSLR.org for more information about WSLR, Inc.\"\n\nThis indicates that the homepage of WSLR-LP is indeed https://www.wslr.org.\n\nTherefore, my response in JSON format would be:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information about the WSLR-LP radio station, including details about its website at `https://www.WSLR.org/` and other online platforms like `wslr.org`. This supports the statement that the homepage of WSLR-LP is `http://www.wslr.org`, as both URLs are consistent with each other."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}